Previously on
The Big Bang Theory...
I guess I'm still wondering
if Emily and I
are right for each other.
Does this have to do with
that girl you had coffee with?
You mean the strong, sexy angel
I can't stop thinking about?
Who can say?
I need to come up with
a big idea to make some money.
There's no reason you can't.
That's easy for you to say.
You and Sheldon already came up
with your
superfluid helium model.
That's just research.
We're never going
to make any money from it.
Forget helium...
the real superfluid
is the fruit punch in this mug.
It reminds me of my daddy's
secret “Don't Tell Mama” juice.
Maybe that's an idea.
Guidance systems
for drunk people.
They have that,
it's called Uber.
Hey, in your supercooled
helium experiments,
did you create
quantum vortices?
Yeah, why?
Well, if you made
a guidance system,
couldn't you use those vortices
as a gyroscope?
Wow. Never thought about that.
And, since it's
in a quantum state,
it would maintain
an infinite persistence.
Groundbreaking
revelations,
tropical drinks.
Tell me this isn't like the best
episode of Sex and the City.